<root>
    <string name="bacon_cheese_heaven">Bacon and Cheese Heaven</string>
    <string name="bacon_wrapped_filet_mignon">Bacon-Wrapped Filet Mignon</string>
    <string name="bbq_chicken_delight">BBQ Chicken Delight</string>
    <string name="bbq_ranch_delight">BBQ Ranch Delight</string>
    <string name="beef_broccoli">Beef and Broccoli</string>
    <string name="berry_smoothie">Berry Smoothie</string>
    <string name="california_roll">California Roll</string>
    <string name="chicago_hotdog">Chicago Hot Dog</string>
    <string name="chicken_avocado">Chicken Avocado</string>
    <string name="chili_cheese_hotdog">Chili Cheese Hot Dog</string>
    <string name="classic_beef_burger">Classic Beef Burger</string>
    <string name="classic_beef_hotdog">Classic Beef Hot Dog</string>
    <string name="coconut_water">Coconut Water</string>
    <string name="dragon_roll">Dragon Roll</string>
    <string name="espresso_martini">Espresso Martini</string>
    <string name="four_cheese_pizza">Four Cheese Pizza</string>
    <string name="garlic_parmesan_chicken">Garlic Parmesan Chicken</string>
    <string name="green_tea_latte">Green Tea Latte</string>
    <string name="grilled_ribeye_steak">Grilled Ribeye Steak</string>
    <string name="hawaiian_bbq_hotdog">Hawaiian BBQ Hot Dog</string>
    <string name="hawaiian_paradise">Hawaiian Paradise</string>
    <string name="honey_mustard_tenders">Honey Mustard Tenders</string>
    <string name="iced_caramel_macchiato">Iced Caramel Macchiato</string>
    <string name="italian_burger">Italian Burger</string>
    <string name="orange_juice">Orange Juice</string>
    <string name="pink_lemonade">Pink Lemonade</string>
    <string name="salted_caramel_brownie">Salted Caramel Brownie</string>
    <string name="spicy_tuna_roll">Spicy Tuna Roll</string>
    <string name="strawberry_cheesecake">Strawberry Cheesecake</string>
    <string name="thai_iced_tea">Thai Iced Tea</string>
    <string name="vegan_burger_delight">Vegan Burger Delight</string>
    <string name="veggie_lovers_pizza">Veggie Lover's Pizza</string>
    <string name="watermelon_smoothie">Watermelon Smoothie</string>
    <string name="bacon_cheese_heaven_desc">A perfect dish for bacon and cheese lovers, bringing an explosion of flavors in every bite.</string>
    <string name="bacon_wrapped_filet_mignon_desc">A succulent filet mignon wrapped in crispy bacon slices, perfect for a gourmet meal.</string>
    <string name="bbq_chicken_delight_desc">Grilled chicken with barbecue sauce, a delicious and flavorful option for barbecue fans.</string>
    <string name="bbq_ranch_delight_desc">A combination of ranch dressing with classic barbecue, bringing the best of both worlds in one dish.</string>
    <string name="beef_broccoli_desc">Tender and flavorful beef served with fresh broccoli, creating a healthy and delicious combination.</string>
    <string name="berry_smoothie_desc">A refreshing and sweet smoothie made with fresh berries, perfect for a healthy snack.</string>
    <string name="california_roll_desc">A traditional California sushi roll made with fresh, high-quality ingredients.</string>
    <string name="chicago_hotdog_desc">The classic Chicago-style hot dog, topped with pickles, mustard, and onions, served in a soft bun.</string>
    <string name="chicken_avocado_desc">A delicious combination of grilled chicken and fresh avocado, perfect for a light meal.</string>
    <string name="chili_cheese_hotdog_desc">A hot dog loaded with spicy chili and melted cheese, perfect for fans of bold flavors.</string>
    <string name="classic_beef_burger_desc">The classic grilled beef burger served on a soft bun with all the traditional toppings.</string>
    <string name="classic_beef_hotdog_desc">The traditional beef hot dog, perfect for a quick and tasty meal.</string>
    <string name="coconut_water_desc">Fresh, natural coconut water, a refreshing and healthy option for any time of the day.</string>
    <string name="dragon_roll_desc">A beautifully crafted and flavorful sushi roll with a perfect mix of fresh seafood.</string>
    <string name="espresso_martini_desc">A sophisticated and elegant cocktail made with fresh espresso and coffee liqueur, ideal for those who enjoy intense flavors.</string>
    <string name="four_cheese_pizza_desc">A delicious and creamy pizza made with an irresistible combination of four cheeses.</string>
    <string name="garlic_parmesan_chicken_desc">Crispy chicken covered with Parmesan cheese and a delicious garlic sauce, an irresistible meal.</string>
    <string name="green_tea_latte_desc">A creamy and smooth drink made with high-quality green tea and steamed milk.</string>
    <string name="grilled_ribeye_steak_desc">A premium cut of grilled ribeye steak, juicy and full of flavor, perfect for meat lovers.</string>
    <string name="hawaiian_bbq_hotdog_desc">A unique hot dog with a Hawaiian twist and barbecue sauce, served with grilled pineapple.</string>
    <string name="hawaiian_paradise_desc">A tropical combination of fresh and exotic flavors, bringing the Hawaiian spirit to your plate.</string>
    <string name="honey_mustard_tenders_desc">Crispy chicken strips covered with a sweet and mildly spicy honey mustard glaze.</string>
    <string name="iced_caramel_macchiato_desc">An iced macchiato made with espresso and a touch of sweet caramel, refreshing for any time of the day.</string>
    <string name="italian_burger_desc">A gourmet burger inspired by Italian flavors, with fresh basil, mozzarella cheese, and marinara sauce.</string>
    <string name="orange_juice_desc">Freshly squeezed orange juice, refreshing and healthy, perfect to start the day.</string>
    <string name="pink_lemonade_desc">A sweet and tangy pink lemonade, perfect for cooling down on hot days.</string>
    <string name="salted_caramel_brownie_desc">A soft and sweet brownie with a touch of salted caramel, an irresistible dessert.</string>
    <string name="spicy_tuna_roll_desc">A spicy sushi roll with fresh tuna, wrapped in seasoned rice and crispy seaweed.</string>
    <string name="strawberry_cheesecake_desc">A delicious slice of strawberry cheesecake made with fresh strawberries and creamy filling.</string>
    <string name="thai_iced_tea_desc">Thai iced tea with milk, sweet and refreshing, an exotic drink.</string>
    <string name="vegan_burger_delight_desc">A delicious vegan burger made with fresh and natural ingredients, full of flavor.</string>
    <string name="veggie_lovers_pizza_desc">A pizza loaded with fresh and flavorful vegetables, perfect for vegetable lovers.</string>
    <string name="watermelon_smoothie_desc">A refreshing and sweet watermelon smoothie, perfect for hot summer days.</string>
</root>